{
  "rounds": [
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "How many children did the fifth most fertile woman have in her lifetime?",
      "solution": "52",
      "answer": "Maddalena Granata - Maddalena Granata (born 1839) Nocera, Italy, who married at 28, had given birth to 52 living and dead children, 49 being males, by 1886. Dr. de Sanctis, of Nocera, stated that she had 15 sets of triplets."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "Breast milk is deficient in Iron and .....",
      "solution": "Vitamin D",
      "answer": "WTE - https://www.whattoexpect.com/first-year/feeding-your-baby/vitamins-and-babies.aspx"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "As per NIH, there are 3 stages of labor: Early & active labor, Delivery of the baby, Delivery of the ....._",
      "solution": "placenta",
      "answer": "NIH."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "The Bishop Score is the most commonly used method to rate the readiness of the ......",
      "solution": "cervix",
      "answer": "NCBI - www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "Starting around week 35, moms-to-be have an increased urge to ....._",
      "solution": "pee",
      "answer": "NIH."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "Lactation consultants often call it 'liquid gold', but there's a scientific name for golden, creamy pre-milk that comes before breast milk is secreted. What's the name?",
      "solution": "Colostrum",
      "answer": "from nuggets of wisdom"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "What is the one flavor that newborn's tastebuds cannot taste?",
      "solution": "Salt",
      "answer": "Tastebuds for salt develops at around 4-6 months of age."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "Lanugo is very thin, soft, usually unpigmented, downy ..... that is sometimes found on the body of a fetal or new-born human.",
      "solution": "hair",
      "answer": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lanugo"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "Witch's ....., that is secreted in around 5% of newborns, is considered a normal physiological occurrence and no treatment or testing is necessary.",
      "solution": "milk",
      "answer": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Witch%27s_milk"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "On an average, how many hours of sleep do parents get in a night for the first year?",
      "solution": "5",
      "answer": "According to healthline.com"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "P letter foods like pears, peaches, prunes help fix .....",
      "solution": "constipation",
      "answer": "(our pediatrician)"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "Spurgeon, Orange and Ples were popular ..... in late 1800s/early 1900s",
      "solution": "names",
      "answer": "the big fat activity book for pregnant people - jordan reid and erin williams"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "On a baby, where would you find the fontanelles?",
      "solution": "head",
      "answer": "Fontanelles allow skull to compress during birth so it can pass through the birth canal."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "The tar-like, sticky black poo that newborns initially poop, is called ....._",
      "solution": "meconium",
      "answer": "Children's Knowledge Bank - Part i."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "A study in 2009 suggested that english speaking toddlers as young as 2, could guess ..... of words.",
      "solution": "plural",
      "answer": "Journal of Child Language in 2009, Jennifer Zapf and Linda Smith,"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“Raising kids is part joy and part ......” — Ed Asner",
      "solution": "guerrilla warfare",
      "answer": "Says the internet. Also look up Ed Asner, because I don't know who he is."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“Having a new baby is like suddenly getting the world’s worst ......” — Anne Lamott",
      "solution": "roommate",
      "answer": "Says the Internet."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“Becoming a mom to me means that you have accepted that for the next 16 years of your life, you will have a sticky ......” - Nia Vardalos",
      "solution": "purse",
      "answer": "intrwbz"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“A two-year old is kind of like having a ....., but you don't have a top for it.” - Jerry Seinfeld",
      "solution": "blender",
      "answer": "GoodHouseKeeping..."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“When I tell my kids I'll do something in a minute, what I'm really saying is 'Please ......'” - @SarcasticMommy4",
      "solution": "forget",
      "answer": "@SarcasticMommy4 twitters."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the toy?",
      "question": "Name this toy - Toy that you place in your baby's bathwater to determine whether it is too hot, presumably because you do not have the hands capable of fulfilling this function.",
      "solution": "Temperature Test Duck",
      "answer": ""
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the toy?",
      "question": "Name this - Plastic giraffes, that are french and thus chic. It was mandatory to own atleast 3. Each costs $28.",
      "solution": "Sophie",
      "answer": "."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the toy?",
      "question": "Name this - Very uncool wheely-thing that allows you to transfer your baby from the car wherever you're going without waking him up, and is therefore the best.",
      "solution": "Snap N Go",
      "answer": "."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the toy?",
      "question": "Name this - A cloth bracelet, intended to be used as a tissue, when you don't have a tissue with you. As a bonus, it allows you to wear your child's boogers with pride.",
      "solution": "Snozzie",
      "answer": "."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the ?",
      "question": "Name this - Ergonomically designed resting area for a nursing baby, aka a pillow. Costs extra because its round.",
      "solution": "Boppy",
      "answer": "."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the ?",
      "question": "Name this - Baby cage, that requires three fully-grown adults and six trips to the computer to figure out how to assemble.",
      "solution": "Pack N Play",
      "answer": "."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the ?",
      "question": "Name this - Sling that you can hang on the door of a public bathroom, so that your baby has somewhere to chill, while you pee.",
      "solution": "Baby Keeper Harness",
      "answer": "."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the ?",
      "question": "Name this - Anatomically correct stuffed woman with removable baby and detachable placenta used to visually communicate to small children EXACTLY how the miracle of childbirth works.",
      "solution": "Birth Doll",
      "answer": "."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Name the ?",
      "question": "Name this - Banana flavored air crackers that you will find crumbs of around your home for the rest of your life.",
      "solution": "Mum Mums",
      "answer": "."
    }
  ]
}
